http://cagesbydesign.com/privacy-policy.html

CagesbyDesign.com is now CustomCages.com! Please Call 800-941-2243 with Questions!
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use and disclosure of your information in connection with your use of our websites, EMAILs, and mobile applications ("Site" or "Sites"). When used herein, the terms "we", "us" and "our" refer to our parent company Adam's Specialty Products, LLC and our brands, our affiliates and subsidiaries. For the purposes of data protection legislation (and with exception to our Reseller partners, described further below), we are a data controller for the information we hold about you in providing our Site.
By visiting this or another Adam's Specialty Products, LLC website displaying this Privacy Policy or a link thereto (a "Website", or collectively the "Websites"), or by otherwise interacting with Adam's Specialty Products, LLC, you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is further subject to the Adam's Specialty Products, LLC Services Agreement related to the Adam's Specialty Products, LLC services you utilize and/or purchase.
When this Privacy Policy uses the term "personal data," we mean any data that relates to an identifiable individual, including their name, address, online identifiers, payment details or email address. The specific data we collect is described in this policy.
We encourage you to read the entire Privacy Policy, which consists of the sections listed below:
Information We Collect
How We Use Your Personal Data
How Long We Keep Your Personal Data
Who We Share Your Personal Data With
Where We Transfer Your Personal Data
How We Keep Your Personal Data Safe
Your Rights In Relation To Your Personal Data
Links To Or From Other Websites
Partner Sites
Children
Changes To This Policy
Resellers and Private Label Partners
Contacting Us
Information We Collect.
Contact information. We collect and retain personal contact information that you submit to us voluntarily in signing up to our products and services or any mailing lists. This includes your name, mailing address, web address, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address. Additionally, we collect contact information provided to us during any correspondence relating to customer support, as well as in connection with products and services offered on our Sites.
Financial Information. We collect and retain financial information you provide when you order our products and services. For example, when you purchase a product or service through Adam's Specialty Products, LLC, we require you to provide a credit card number and billing address before we process that application.
Information on your use of the Site. We collect information about the device with which your use of the Sites and information on your use of the Site itself, such as the domain name, Internet Service Provider, browser type and version, pages viewed, information accessed, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address you use to connect to the Internet. We also collect information in relation to Cookies – for more information, please review our policy on cookies.
Demographic Information. We collect and store demographic information (your postcode, gender and age). We may also collect and store demographic information (such as your zip code, gender and age), and use this data to tailor your experience on our Websites, ensure you are at least 18 years of age to make purchases, provide content that we think you might be interested in, perform general improvements to the Websites, and display the content according to your preferences. Such demographic information may be shared with partners, market researchers and other third parties on an aggregate, non-personally identifiable basis. No personally identifiable information will be linked to such aggregated demographic information that is shared with third parties.
Telephone Recording and Monitoring. To ensure Adam's Specialty Products, LLC customers receive quality service, Adam's Specialty Products, LLC selects phone calls for recording and/or monitoring. These calls, between Adam's Specialty Products, LLC customers (or potential customers) and employees, are evaluated by supervisors and/or other Adam's Specialty Products, LLC representatives. This is to guarantee that prompt, consistent assistance and accurate information is delivered in a professional manner.
How We Use Your Personal Data.
To perform our contract with you. We use this information to perform our contract with you and fulfil your requests, such as:
Sending you requested service information:
Fulfilling your order;
Billing for services;
Creating directories (only when you explicitly ask to be included);
Responding to customer service requests, questions and concerns; and
Administering your account.
Note that, generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are transactional and not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to cancel your services with us.
We also engage other companies, individuals, and affiliates of Adam's Specialty Products, LLC to perform certain functions and services for you. These third parties:
process credit card payments;
provide marketing assistance; and
remove duplicate information from customer lists.
To contact you. If you have given your consent to send you EMAIL, phone or SMS marketing, or if you have provided us with your postal address, we will use the personal data you give to us to contact you from time to time. If you register on the Site, you can choose to provide your consent to receive marketing communications by e-mail, phone and/or cell number (including use of automated dialing equipment and/or pre-recorded calls), text (SMS) message, social networks or any other means of communication that your device may be capable of receiving (i.e. video, etc.). If you do not want to receive postal or electronic communications, you may withdraw your consent at any time, by clicking the link in a communication, or EMAILing us using the address provided below.
Directory Listings. If you provide your information in order to be included in our free directories you are consenting to (1) individuals contacting you to solicit your products and services and (2) businesses contacting you to market services you may find useful. Due to the nature of a directory, your information will be published publicly and you may be contacted by phone or EMAIL depending on the information you provide. You will never be added to our directories unless you request to be included and you may remove your listing at any time by calling (920) 886-1220 or sending us an EMAIL.
Promotional Offers and Sweepstakes. If you provide your name for a promotional offer or to enter a sweepstakes or contest and you win a prize, we will post a winner's list online where your name and city will be listed for our promotional purposes and to demonstrate the transparency of a competition, and we will file your name with state agencies if required by law.
To protect our Site and our business. We monitor use of the Sites and we use the information we collect, including personal data, to pursue our legitimate interest in protecting you, others and the Site itself by:
identifying fraudulent activities and transactions;
preventing abuse of the Sites and investigating and/or seeking prosecution for any potential threats to or misuse of the Sites;
ensuring compliance with the applicable terms of service and this Privacy Policy;
investigating violations of or enforcing these agreements; and
otherwise protecting the rights and property of Adam's Specialty Products, LLC, its partners, and customers.
To improve our services. In order to pursue our legitimate interest in improving our Sites, we also use personal data to conduct research and analysis and to identify what services you and other customers like you need:
to better understand how people interact with our websites to provide communications about products which we think will be of interest to you; and
to determine the effectiveness of promotional campaigns and advertising.
Whenever we process data for these purposes we will ensure that we always keep your personal data rights in high regard and take account of these rights. You have the right to object to this processing if you wish and if you wish to do so, please click here to update your communication preferences. Please bear in mind that if you object this may affect our ability to carry out tasks above for your benefit.
*For services in the United States, by registering on a Website and providing your telephone number, you agree that this action constitutes a purchase, inquiry and/or application for purposes of telemarketing laws. Regardless of the fact that your telephone and/or cell number may be listed with the Federal Do-Not-Call Registry or your local State Do-Not-Call list, you are providing your express written consent to receive future information (including telemarketing) about products and services from us and/or our affiliates, and you hereby agree and consent to our contacting you using the information you have provided and will provide to us. This means we may contact you by e-mail, phone and/or cell number (including use of automated dialing equipment and/or pre-recorded calls), text (SMS) message, social networks or any other means of communication that your wireless or other telecommunications device may be capable of receiving (i.e. video, etc.). We may also send you information or offers from time to time to the postal address or EMAIL address we have on file (as further outlined in this Privacy Policy).
How Long We Keep Your Personal Data.
We keep information only for as long as we need it to provide you services, manage our business or as required by law or contract. Where you have a contract with us, we will retain your data for the length of the contract, and will further retain that information for a time period consistent with our legal or regulatory responsibilities, after you terminate all your services with us to resolve disputes, enforce our relevant Service Agreement, and to adhere to the technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of the Sites. If you have any questions about how long we will keep your specific data, please send us an EMAIL.
Who We Share Your Personal Data With.
We provide your personal data to companies that help us with our business activities (e.g. assisting us in Site operations, providing customer service, etc.) or that assist us in improving our products, content, services or advertising. These companies are authorized to use your personal data only as necessary to provide these services. When you ask to be part of our directories, the information you provide will be displayed publicly.
We will also share your personal data:
As required by law, court order or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency in order to enforce or apply our Services Agreement or other agreements.
When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a government request. This includes exchanging information with law enforcement, other companies and organizations for fraud protection, credit risk reduction or other similar purposes.
In connection with a corporate change including a merger, acquisition, transfer or sale of assets or in connection to insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership. Information about our users, including customer information, will also need to be disclosed to our legal and financial advisors, investors or potential buyer in some commercial transactions seeking financing, investment or support or funding.
To any other third party where we have your prior informed consent to do so.
To other entities belonging to Adam's Specialty Products, LLC (i.e. any companies directly or indirectly controlled by Adam's Specialty Products, LLC). A list of our companies is included here including their vendors, suppliers, contractors and agents, which may be involved in the provision of the Website or the content, so that we can better serve you or, simply, to give response to your requests (e.g. when you use contact us forms).
Where We Transfer Your Personal Data.
Our Sites are operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States.
EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield. Adam's Specialty Products, LLC and all of its subsidiaries (namely, CustomAquariums.com, CustomCages.com, LifetimeAquariums.com, SerenityUSA.com, Visionproducts.us, Cagesunder500dollars.com) participate in and comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce with respect to the collection, use and retention of personal information that is transferred from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland to the United States (collectively, the "Framework"). To learn more about the Privacy Shield program and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/. To provide adequate protection for certain EU Personal Data and Swiss Personal Data about corporate customers, clients, suppliers, and business partners received in the U.S., Adam's Specialty Products, LLC has elected to self-certify to the Framework administered by the U.S. Department of Commerce ("Privacy Shield"). Adam's Specialty Products, LLC adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement, and Liability. Adam's Specialty Products, LLC is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and for any subsequent transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Adam's Specialty Products, LLC complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions. For purposes of enforcing compliance with the Privacy Shield, Adam's Specialty Products, LLC is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the United States Federal Trade Commission with regard to our compliance with the Privacy Shield. Adam's Specialty Products, LLC may be required to disclose personal information to law enforcement, regulatory or other government agencies, or to other third parties, in each case to comply with legal, regulatory, or national security obligations or requests.
Adam's Specialty Products, LLC commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Adam's Specialty Products, LLC by EMAIL. We will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints or disputes within 45 days of receiving your complaint. Adam's Specialty Products, LLC's independent recourse mechanism for Privacy Shield complaints for use by EU and Swiss individuals is MEDIATION. You may have the option to select binding arbitration for the resolution of your complaint under certain circumstances, provided you have taken the following steps: (1) raised your complaint directly with Adam's Specialty Products, LLC and provided us the opportunity to resolve the issue; (2) made use of the independent dispute resolution mechanism identified above; and (3) raised the issue through the relevant data protection authority and allowed the US Department of Commerce an opportunity to resolve the complaint at no cost to you. If you have any questions about this Adam's Specialty Products, LLC participation in the Privacy Shield Framework please contact us as follows: EMAIL or by mail at Adam's Specialty Products, LLC, Attn: Privacy Officer, 7260 Commerce Plaza Dr, Neenah, WI 54956.
How We Keep Your Personal Data Safe.
We work to protect the security of your financial information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") software, which encrypts the information you input on the Site. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is completely secure and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. You can further help to ensure your security by taking a few simple precautions. For instance, it is important to protect against unauthorized access to your computer and to any Adam's Specialty Products, LLC username and password, and to be sure to sign off when you are finished using a shared computer.
Your Rights in Relation to Your Personal Data.
You will be entitled to ask us:
For access to a copy of your personal data;
To correct, erase or restrict our processing of your personal data;
To transfer the information you have provided under contract or consent to another organization;
To stop processing your information, by withdrawing your consent or objecting to our legitimate interests.
Your rights in relation to your personal data are limited in some situations. For example, if we have a legal requirement or a compelling legitimate ground we may continue to process your information. We will provide you with information on whether there are limits or exemptions that apply to any request that you make.
For our EU resident customers, you can view or change the information you have provided us by submitting a request through EMAIL or logging into your online account manager, if applicable. Due to the nature of your request you may be asked for additional forms of identification.
For all other customers, please send your questions or concerns to our EMAIL. You may also access your information by logging into your online account manager, if applicable.
And as always, all of our customers that simply wish to unsubscribe from our communications may do so by following the unsubscribe link found either at the bottom of any of our marketing EMAILs or within the footer of many of our Sites.
Please note, in no event will financial information be provided over the phone, nor will such information be provided without verification.
You also have the right to make a complaint if you feel your personal data has been mishandled by contacting us via EMAIL. We encourage you to come to us in the first instance but, to the extent that this right applies to you, you are entitled to complain directly to the relevant supervisory authority. This can be the supervisory authority where you reside or work, or where you believe a breach has taken place.
Links to Or From Other Websites.
Adam's Specialty Products, LLC has no control over and is not responsible for the privacy policies or information gathering practices of other websites, including those to which we may link and those which may link to us. We recommend that you review privacy policies of every online service you use before submitting any personal data and direct any concerns to the site administrator of that website.
Partner Sites.
Adam's Specialty Products, LLC sometimes enters into agreements in which we jointly develop or operate websites with third parties (each a "Partner Site"). Any information collected via a Partner Site may be jointly owned by Adam's Specialty Products, LLC and the applicable third-party partner, or, alternatively, owned solely by us or the third-party partner. In such event we will make sure you know who is collecting your data when it is collected as well as which privacy policy applies.
Children.
You must be at least eighteen years old to register online or purchase our goods or services. Adam's Specialty Products, LLC does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of eighteen.
Changes To This Policy.
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time, and will communicate changes to this Policy via EMAIL to users who have provided an EMAIL address and post a notice on our Site prior to the change becoming effective.
Resellers and Private Label Partners.
As it relates to Adam's Specialty Products, LLC's trusted resellers and private label partners (collectively, "Resellers"), Adam's Specialty Products, LLC may process customer Personal Data on behalf of Reseller. In such cases, Reseller is the data controller and Adam's Specialty Products, LLC is the data processor and each party's obligations will be outlined in the Reseller Agreement between the parties. In the event of a data subject access request sent by a third party to a Reseller, Reseller will make a similar request to Adam's Specialty Products, LLC by sending EMAIL, and submitting the appropriate form and data. All data collected through this relationship will be treated in accordance with this policy.
Contacting Us.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you can contact us by writing to us at EMAIL or by mail at 7260 Commerce Plaza Dr., Neenah, WI, 54956 - Attention: Privacy Team.
Finch AviaryFinch CagesGreenwing Macaw CagesBird Aviaries for BanksBird Aviaries for Dentist Offices
Please enter your email address below to subscribe to exciting updates and product offers!
Name
Email
Subscribe
Copyright © 2020 Adam's Specialty Products, LLC. All Rights Reserved.
Sign in
Please enter your email below and we will send you a new password.
